So you can find videos on many channels
but in today's episode I am going to
tell you that within a very short time, within
five minutes, you can do third party
insurance at home. Those are
smartphone apps. I am going to show
you all this in your smartphone. So,
okay friends,
in the capital, we can do third party insurance or
any other insurance very easily
on policybazaar.com by
comparing and charging for the purpose.
Friends, before starting, if you
want to buy something, then definitely like, like, like and
subscribe
in your hand. If you do
n't like me, then only you will do it. So, if you
subscribe here, then here
you have to open the fast, if you want to mix any bike,
car, blood, boil or anything, then first of all
go and do
research on policybazaar.com,
see a lot of complete information there. Babuji, you have
only one computer for Congress, you will get it at the police station,
here I will
take all the research to you so that you have
all the information in case of any kind, I will
find it on your smartphone that  I search
policybazaar.com, then I am
using it on my smartphone, so you
can also do it on your smartphone, it is not a big deal and
here we do masturbation which is the first
option, thanks for subscribing and
yes you can subscribe to winters or anyone
here, so currently there is two
wheeler insurance, so I have to
go over it and here whatever you enter here,
like I enter that
information,
after entering it on your bike, all the information will
come inside your smartphone, your
bike number, model number, etc., then you
need to select anything to search everything, normally it will automatically
take your information of the vehicle according to the number, then it is
asking whether your cut
polices have expired or not,
then mine have expired and have increased more than that, I
click on it mode in fly and
after doing morning support, then we have to click on third party only
here by applying low pressure from the
wrong  You will see more plans
and here you have to click on third party
and this plan with a person
accident when and this boxing which I am talking about
some personal accident cover, if you take this then
you will get to see 30 more and for
now I select the national shoulder plan here, the
sensitive one
is a good plan and after selecting this some
such information will come, okay this will be my first step
and here you will have to make your base
or after completing the step now
go to scientists and go to the second step,
here you will find out the normal name and you have to
enter the prescription name, this is something like this, if you have to
take insurance then
Juhi is the nominee,
Pooja Pandey gets the entire amount, then here I
enter Papa ji's name, I
stop and Junoon is who does he seem to be, at
present the nominee has
heard Khokhar on that question, perhaps I have seized it at the moment and the police
must check your Ritesh October 2 2010 registration date, okay  This is the
seven process,
after completing the three steps of the entire day, you will have to go to the
last payment option here
and here the
accident cover which will be compulsory, which I told you about the
feedback from Indian Excise, you will have to
take it completely compulsory,
so you will have to take it and you
must check your details once,
after the complete information here,
before making the payment, you must check your
personal details here, Dharmendra Singh Raj Singh
and tell your address, check it, check the phone
number, this is the vehicle number from third party insurance
and after
checking all these things, after that you have to pay your Paytm Secure Life
Secure Life in a completely
secure manner and currently it is
asking for the payment gateway, whatever your payment is, you
can make the payment accordingly, make the payment quickly,
currently by making payment to two directions, you have to do the
communication from this side through
any method, I am doing it through an alarm debit
card, after the channel transaction is
successful, you will see the
download policy option here.  Download the police from a few places
and here you do
not need to get any self-attested test done anywhere, there
is no need to do anything at any time, now you can
download your police from here and
show it, your channel will not be cut and
it will remain valid, if it is a recording for any purpose then this is all
in this video, if you have any
question or suggestion about this then
definitely leave a comment, I will definitely reply
and if you liked the video then please like,
subscribe and say I am amazing